Edward R. Murrow Papers MS025
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Professional employment, 1934 -- 1973; MS025.003; 42.35 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1934 -- 1973; MS025.003.002; 41.25 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s)
    - CBS - Programs - See It Now, 1934 -- 1958; MS025.003.002.17; 5.5 Linear Feet; 10 Digital Object(s)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IG1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.113.00399 (Box 113)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IG2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.113.00400 (Box 113)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IG3, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.113.00401 (Box 113)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IG4, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.113.00402 (Box 113)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IH1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00403 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IH2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00404 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IH3, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00405 (Box 114)
        Microfilm Reel 42. Includes correspondence to/from McCarthy concerning his appearance on "See It Now"
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #1: New York State Legislature, Joint Committee Investigating Seditious Activities. Revolutionary readicalism, its history, ... purpose and tactics...being the report of the Joint Legislative Committee Investigating Seditious Activities. Albany, J.B. Lyon Co., 1920. 4 Vols. Part I, Revolutionary and Subversive Movements Abroad and At Home, Vol. II)., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00001 (Box 114)
          Still image from the April 6, 1954 McCarthy rebuttal on "See It Now"
          See It Now; Communism; Army-McCarthy Controversy, 1954; Murrow, Edward R.; McCarthy, Joseph Raymond; CBS
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #2: Fish Committee Hearings. U.S. Congress, House, Special Committee to Investigate Communist Activities in the United States 71st Congress, 2d Sessions Hearings pursuant to H. Res. 220. Part 5 - Volume No. 3. Los Angeles, CA, October 8 and 9, 1930., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00002 (Box 114)
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #3: Fish Committee Report.H. Report 2290, 71st Congress, 3rd Session. Report of the Special Committee to Investigate Communist Activities in the United States, pursuant to H. Res. 220 (Mr. Fish from the Special Committee... January 17, 1931)., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00003 (Box 114)
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #4: House 2100. Report of the Special Committee to Investigate the Activities Within this Commonwealth of Communist, Fascist, Nazi and Other Subversive Organizations So Called. Under Chapter 32, Resolves of 1937. Revised Edition, Printed Under Chapter 87 of the Resolves of 1938., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00004 (Box 114)
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #5: U.S. Congress, House, Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Investigation of Un-American Propaganda Activities in the United States. Hearings Before a Special Committee on Un-American Activities. House of Representatives, 75th Congress, 3rd Session on House Resolution 282. August 12-23, 1938., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00005 (Box 114)
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #6: Dies Committee Report. House Report 2, 76th Congress, 1st Session. Report of the House Special Committee on Un-American Activities, entitled, "Investigation of Un-American Activities and Propaganda...pursuant to H. Res. 282. (75th Congress)" January 3, 1939, MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00006 (Box 114)
        - From McCarthy Program (4/6/1954) stills. Senator McCarthy reviews Communist Citation #7: Fourth Report, Un-American Activities in California, 1948. Communist Front Organizations. Report of the Joint Factfinding Committee to the 1948 Regular California Legislature, Sacramento, 1948., MS025.003.002.17.114.00405.00007 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IH4, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00406 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00407 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00408 (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II3, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00409a (Box 114)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II3, 1934 -- 1954; MS025.003.002.17.114.00409b (Box 114)
        Microfilm Reel 42. Folder includes material about Moscow University Summer Programs in 1934 and 1935 (organized with help of IIE; includes IIE reports). Also included are pleas for Murrow to publicize disappearance of US citizens in Eastern Europe in the late 1940s.
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II4, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00410 (Box 115)
        Microfilm Reel 42. File empty when received.
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II5, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00411 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II6, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00412 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II7, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00413 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File II8, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00414 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00415 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ4, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00416 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ5, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00417 (Box 115)
        Microfilm Reel 43.
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ9, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00418 (Box 115)
        Microfilm Reel 43. File empty when received.
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ10, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00419 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ11, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00420 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ12, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00421 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ14, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00422 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ15, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00423 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ20, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00424 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ24, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00425 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ25, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00426 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IJ26, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00427 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IK1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00428 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IK3, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00429 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IL, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.115.00430 (Box 115)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIA1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00431 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIA16, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00432 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIA17, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00433 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIB, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00434 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIC, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00435 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIE, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00436 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIF, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00437 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIA2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00438 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIA3, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00439 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIB, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00440 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIE1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00441 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIE2, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00442 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIF, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00443 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIG1, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00444 (Box 116)
      - Matter of "M" - Reference File IIIH, 1954; MS025.003.002.17.116.00445 (Box 116)
    - CBS - Programs - Small World, 1958 -- 1959; MS025.003.002.18; 0.55 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
      Represented in this section are scripts for four "Small World" programs and one folder of correspondence, 1954-60, which is arranged in reverse chronological order. This list provides data on the interiewees for the four programs.
      - Correspondence, 1958; MS025.003.002.18.116.00446 (Box 116)
        - Harry S. Truman and Clement Richard Atlee on "Small World" November 30, 1958., MS025.003.002.18.116.00446.00001 (Box 116)
          Truman appears in top left and bottom right of photo; Clement appears in top right and bottom left of photo.
          Small World; US Presidents; Politician; Murrow, Edward R.; Truman, Harry S.; Atlee, Clement Richard; CBS
      - Scripts, 1958 -- 1959; MS025.003.002.18.116.00447 (Box 116)
        Nehru, Jawaharlal - Delhi; Dewey, Gov. Thomas - Portland, Maine; Huxley, Aldous - Turin, Italy (Oct. 12, 1958) / Beecham, Sir Thomas - Nice, France; Borge, Victor - Southbury, Conn.; Callas, Maria - Milan, Italy (Jan. 4, 1959) / Crankshaw, Edward - England; Jackson, Barbara Ward - Honolulu; Stevenson, Adlai - San Francisco (Feb. 22, 1959) / Kennedy, Senator John F. - Atlantic City; Menon, Krishna - United Nations; Boothby, Lord Robert - London (Oct. 18, 1959).
    - CBS - Programs - Sunday Broadcasts, 1941 -- 1947; MS025.003.002.19; 1.65 Linear Feet
      "Sunday Broadcasts" are represented by scripts, July 12, 1942 to March 3, 1946, arranged in chronological order. In some cases correspondence and cables are filed with a particular script. Number 453 includes miscellaneous correspondence and scripts which cover the wartime and postwar periods.
      - Scripts, 1942 -- 1943; MS025.003.002.19.116.00448 (Box 116)
      - Scripts, 1943 -- 1944; MS025.003.002.19.116.00449 (Box 116)
      - Scripts, 1944; MS025.003.002.19.117.00450 (Box 117)
      - Scripts, 1944 -- 1945; MS025.003.002.19.117.00451 (Box 117)
        Microfilm Reel 43. Pulled original broadcast script from Paris due to high acidiy and deteriorating condition. Photocopy of script remains in folder Jan 14, 2008; see box 39090015515774y
      - Scripts, 1945 -- 1946; MS025.003.002.19.117.00452 (Box 117)
      - Correspondence and Scripts, 1941 -- 1947; MS025.003.002.19.117.00453 (Box 117)
        Microfilm Reel 43. Also includes material related to the 1941 publication of 'This is London' by Edward R. Murrow and a commencement speech by Edward R. Murrow 'America as an Island' given sometime after the war.
      - Original Paris scripts, 1941 -- 1944; MS025.003.002.19.252.0001 (Box 252)
        Pulled from MS.025/003/001/19/117:451 as oversize and too fragile. Photocopies of report in original box.
    - CBS - Programs - This I Believe, 1954 -- 1958; MS025.003.002.20; 0.55 Linear Feet
      This one file contains correspondence, 1954-58, and a copy of a promotional book for this broadcast series.
      - Correspondence and Promotional Material, 1954 -- 1958; MS025.003.002.20.117.00454 (Box 117)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Original exists in duplicate. Housed in MS025/006.008-002#00008, location: 39090011518491
    - CBS - Programs - Years of Crisis, 1950 -- 1960; MS025.003.002.21; 1.1 Linear Feet
      With the exception of 1954, there are scripts for each yearly broadcast from 1950-58. For some years there are two scripts, as written and the broadcast version. There is also one folder of general correspondence regarding this program.
      - Correspondence, 1950 -- 1960; MS025.003.002.21.117.00455 (Box 117)
        Microfilm Reel 44.
      - Script, 1950; MS025.003.002.21.118.00456 (Box 118)
      - Script, 1951; MS025.003.002.21.118.00457 (Box 118)
      - Script - 1952 Program, MS025.003.002.21.118.00458 (Box 118)
      - Script - 1953 Program, MS025.003.002.21.118.00459 (Box 118)
      - Script - 1955 Program, MS025.003.002.21.118.00460 (Box 118)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Includes a note from Carl Sandburg.
      - Script, 1956; MS025.003.002.21.118.00461 (Box 118)
      - Script, 1957; MS025.003.002.21.118.00462 (Box 118)
      - Script, 1958; MS025.003.002.21.118.00463 (Box 118)
    - CBS - Programs - Special Programs, 1934 -- 1972; MS025.003.002.22; 1.65 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
      This section contains files for forty special programs, mostly aired over CBS, with which Murrow was involved in some manner. The files vary as to contents, the most complete containing correspondence, memoranda, newsclippings, and scripts. Some files just contain a synopsis of the program or a script.
      - Whither Britain?, CBS-BBC Scripts, 1934; MS025.003.002.22.118.00464 (Box 118)
        H. G. Wells (Jan. 9, 1934); Winston Churchill (Jan. 16, 1934); Very Reverend Walter R. Matthews, Dean of Exeter (Jan. 23, 1934); Ernest Bevan (Jan. 30, 1934); George Bernard Shaw (Feb. 6, 1934); Margaret Haig, Viscountess Rhonda, script missing (March 6, 1934); Lloyd George (March 30, 1934).
      - Talk About America, BBC, 1942; MS025.003.002.22.118.00465 (Box 118)
      - Orchestrated Hell, CBS World News, 1943; MS025.003.002.22.118.00466 (Box 118)
      - Edward R. Murrow in Los Angeles, CBS-KNX, 1945; MS025.003.002.22.118.00467 (Box 118)
      - Jan Masaryk, CBS-Radio, 1948; MS025.003.002.22.118.00468 (Box 118)
      - CBS Views the Press, Notes on the News by E. R. Murrow, MS025.003.002.22.118.00469 (Box 118)
      - CBS Election Preview on U.S. Elections, BBC, 1948; MS025.003.002.22.118.00470 (Box 118)
      - Invitation to Learning, Murrow with Lyman Bryson and Clyde Kluckhohn, CBS-Radio, 1949; MS025.003.002.22.118.00471 (Box 118)
      - Sunday with Murrow, CBS-Radio, 1949; MS025.003.002.22.118.00472 (Box 118)
      - Appeal for Destitute Shallmar, Maryland, CBS-Radio, 1949; MS025.003.002.22.118.00473 (Box 118)
      - Midcentury Report - Roundtable discussion on the last 50 years and evaluation of prospective trends for the next 50 years, CBS-Radio, 1950; MS025.003.002.22.119.00474 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. With Sevareid, Lesueur, Smith, Downs, Schoenbrun, Burdett, and Costello.
      - Draft Smart Students? CBS-Radio, 1951; MS025.003.002.22.119.00475 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Student Deferment.
      - You and the World, CBS-Radio, 1952; MS025.003.002.22.119.00476 (Box 119)
      - Answer the Call, broadcast to launch American Red Cross annual drive, CBS-Radio, 1953; MS025.003.002.22.119.00477 (Box 119)
      - The Green Border, Refugee Tide from Iron Curtain Countries, CBS-Radio, 1953; MS025.003.002.22.119.00478 (Box 119)
      - Conservation in the Oil Industry, CBS-TV, 1953; MS025.003.002.22.119.00479 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Panel discussion with five Oil Executives.
      - Ticket to Freedom, Ford 50th Anniversary Show, CBS-TV, 1953; MS025.003.002.22.119.00480 (Box 119)
      - Resources for Freedom, A summary of Volume One of the Report of the President's Materials Policy Commission. W.S. Paley, Chairman, CBS-TV, 1954; MS025.003.002.22.119.00481 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Produced by the Public Affairs Division.
      - McCarthy Program, "See It Now," and McCarthy's Rebuttal, CBS-TV (Mar. 1 & Apr. 6, 1954), MS025.003.002.22.119.00482 (Box 119)
      - The Expendables, Studio One, 1954; MS025.003.002.22.119.00483 (Box 119)
      - Invitation to Learning, Murrow with Lyman Bryson and James Reston, CBS-Radio, 1954; MS025.003.002.22.119.00484 (Box 119)
      - The Terrible Rain, Conditions in Putnam, Connecticut, CBS-Radio, 1955; MS025.003.002.22.119.00485 (Box 119)
      - List of Other Programs, 1954 -- 1956; MS025.003.002.22.119.00486 (Box 119)
      - The World Tonight, Thoughts on conditions When a British Prime Minister Resigns, CBS-Radio, 1957; MS025.003.002.22.119.00487 (Box 119)
      - The Galindez-Murphy Case: A Chronicle of Terror, CBS-Radio, 1957; MS025.003.002.22.119.00488 (Box 119)
      - Who Killed Michael Farmer? CBS-Radio, 1958; MS025.003.002.22.119.00489 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. A in-depth analysis of factors involved in juvenile crime.
        - Edward R. Murrow at microphone, MS025.003.002.22.119.00489.00001 (Box 119)
          Negative: MS025.002.045.00261b.00008. Included with promotion kit for "Who Killed Michael Farmer" 1958. Caption on back: "Edward R. Murrow. Narrator. 'Who Killed Michael Farmer?' CBS Radio." No Date available
      - POW - A Study in Survival, CBS-Radio, 1958; MS025.003.002.22.119.00490 (Box 119)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Korean War, the actions and reactions of American prisoners in a Communist Chinese camp.
      - The Hidden Revolution Series, CBS-Radio, 1958; MS025.003.002.22.120.00491 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 44. First Program of 6 documentaries dealing with with momentous issues facing mankind currently, narrated by Murrow.
      - List of Other Programs, 1957 -- 1958; MS025.003.002.22.120.00492 (Box 120)
      - The Business of Sex, CBS-Radio, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00493 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 44. Murrow, Narrator, with anthropoligist margaret Mead, New York Commisioner of Corrections Anna Kross, psychologist Harold Greenwald, and associate editor of "America" Fr. Benjamin Masse, S.
      - The Missing Class of '59, CBS-TV, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00494 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 44. The account of Norfolk, Virginia action of shutting all schools rather than permitting 17 Negro students to sit with 10,000 Whites.
      - Montgomery Speaks His Mind, CBS-TV, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00495 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. Interview by Murrow and Collingwood - Field Marshall Montgomery at his home.
      - Of Knobby Knees and Summer Breeze, CBS-Radio, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00496 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. On the conformity of male dress.
      - How Britain Votes, CBS-Radio, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00497 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. Comments on British Elections.
      - After the Battle, BBC-TV, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00498 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. Correspondents who had covered the War surveyed the 14 years since it ended.
      - List of Other Programs, 1959; MS025.003.002.22.120.00499 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45.
      - The Week that Shook the World, CBS-TV, 1960; MS025.003.002.22.120.00500 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. Replay of tapes recorded by Murrow, Sevareid and Shire the week before the start of World War II, narrated by Walter Cronkite.
      - Prime Minister Jawaharlal Nehru Interviewed at the United Nations by John McVane of ABC, Frank Bourgholtzer of NBC, and Daniel Schorr of CBS, UN-TV, 1960; MS025.003.002.22.120.00501 (Box 120)
      - List of Other Programs, 1960; MS025.003.002.22.120.00502 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. The Year of the Polaris (Oct. 11, 1960)
      - Field Marshall Montgomery Interview, BBC-TV, 1961; MS025.003.002.22.120.00503 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. Based on his book, "Leadership."
      - Harry S. Truman, 1884-1972, CBS-TV, MS025.003.002.22.120.00504 (Box 120)
        Microfilm Reel 45. CBS Special reporter, Walter Cronkite. (Note: refer to "See it Now" Program on 2/2/58, "From Precinct to President").
    - CBS - Radio/TV/Broacasting Evaluations, 1946 -- 1961; MS025.003.002.23; 0.55 Linear Feet
      One file of correspondence, memoranda, newsclippings, and reports relating to evaluations of radio and television broadcasting over the years.
      - Radio/TV Broadcast Evaluations, 1946 -- 1961; MS025.003.002.23.120.00505 (Box 120)
  - United States Information Agency, 1953 -- 1968; MS025.003.003; 1.1 Linear Feet
    Murrow's files as director of the United States Information Agency are housed in the National Archives, Washington, D.C. The small amount of material contained here represents copies of Murrow's statement before the Senate confirmation hearing, copies of his reports and speeches, and his personal correspondence as director.
    - Murrow Statement at Senate Hearing, 1961; MS025.003.003.120.00506 (Box 120)
    - Correspondence, 1953 -- 1968; MS025.003.003.120.00507 (Box 120)
    - Reports, 1960 -- 1965; MS025.003.003.121.00508 (Box 121)
    - Speeches, 1961 -- 1962; MS025.003.003.121.00509a (Box 121)
    - Speeches, 1962 -- 1963; MS025.003.003.121.00509b (Box 121)
- Activities, 1941 -- 1969; MS025.004; 6.8 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains files related to Murrow's professional activities. The series is further subdivided into the following subseries: albums, organizations, publications, scripts and speeches.
  - Albums, 1948 -- 1959; MS025.004.001; 1.1 Linear Feet
    Incomplete files for five of Murrow's Albums constitute this part. Those files for "I Can Hear It Now" and "Sir Winston Churchill" are the most complete and contain correspondence, memoranda, financial records, newsclippings and promotional material.
    - I Can Hear It Now, 1948 -- 1950; MS025.004.001.121.00510a (Box 121)
      Microfilm Reel 46.
    - I Can Hear It Now, 1950 -- 1959; MS025.004.001.121.00510b (Box 121)
    - I Can Hear It Now, Columbia Records, 1948 -- 1951; MS025.004.001.121.00511 (Box 121)
    - Israel Album Project, 1950 -- 1953; MS025.004.001.121.00512 (Box 121)
    - Edward R. Murrow - A Reporter Remembers, Vols. 1 & 2, MS025.004.001.121.00513 (Box 121)
    - Sir Winston Churchill, 1955 -- 1957; MS025.004.001.122.00514 (Box 122)
    - This I Believe, 1953; MS025.004.001.122.00515 (Box 122)
  - Organizations, 1941 -- 1967; MS025.004.002; 4.4 Linear Feet
    This part contains the files for 35 organizations with which Murrow was associated, either as a participant, member, or as an officer or member of the board of directors. The organizations are arranged in alphabetical order by title, with material in each file arranged in reverse chronological order. The types and quantity of material for each organization varies, but usually correspondence, memoranda, newsclippings, press releases, minutes, speeches, and printed matter are available. A listing of the organizations, with inclusive dates of the correspondence for each, is provided.
    - Air Age Neighbor Movement, 1941 -- 1950; MS025.004.002.122.00516 (Box 122)
    - American Fund for Czechoslovak Refugees, 1958 -- 1959; MS025.004.002.122.00517 (Box 122)
    - Anne Frank Foundation, 1958; MS025.004.002.122.00518 (Box 122)
    - Association of Radio/TV Analysts, 1942 -- 1961; MS025.004.002.122.00519 (Box 122)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1947 -- 1960; MS025.004.002.122.00520 (Box 122)
    - Burning Tree Club, 1950 -- 1959; MS025.004.002.122.00521 (Box 122)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1950 -- 1952; MS025.004.002.123.00522a (Box 123)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1953; MS025.004.002.123.00522b (Box 123)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1954; MS025.004.002.123.00522c (Box 123)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1955; MS025.004.002.123.00522d (Box 123)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1955; MS025.004.002.124.00522e (Box 124)
      Microfilm Reel 47.
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1956; MS025.004.002.124.00522f (Box 124)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1957 -- 1965; MS025.004.002.124.00522g (Box 124)
    - CBS Foundation, Board of Directors, 1956 -- 1959; MS025.004.002.124.00523 (Box 124)
    - CBS Foundation, News and Public Affairs Fellowships, 1957 -- 1959; MS025.004.002.124.00524 (Box 124)
    - The Century Association, 1948 -- 1960; MS025.004.002.125.00525 (Box 125)
    - Clubs, miscellaneous, 1948 -- 1961; MS025.004.002.125.00526 (Box 125)
    - Columbia Lecture Bureau, 1949 -- 1951; MS025.004.002.125.00527 (Box 125)
    - Committee on Present Danger, 1950 -- 1952; MS025.004.002.125.00528 (Box 125)